(Penny:)Oh. Well, you know,
I've got two hands
(Penny:)and a bit of a drinking problem.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
Ask a silly question.
(Sheldon:)-That's odd.
-What?
(Sheldon:)There are takeout containers
in the trash can.
(Penny:)So? That's my dinner from last night.
(Sheldon:)What's odd is they're
in the trash can.
(Penny:)Okay. Look, honey,
I promise there's no one's here.
I've had a long day. I just want
to have a quiet dinner by myself.
(Sheldon:)Oh, very well.
(Sheldon:)I'm no stranger to enjoying
the pleasures of solitude.
(Sheldon:)-Oh!
-What?
(Sheldon:)Have you gotten Leonard
a welcome-home gift yet?
(Sheldon:)-No.
-Oh, great.
(Sheldon:)Do you want to go halfsies
on a 200 dollar squirt gun?
(Bernadette:)-Hi, honey.
-Hey.
(Bernadette:)I made some brownies.
You want one?
(Howard:)You're kidding, right?
(Howard:)I mean, you know
I'm trying to lose weight.
(Howard:)God, I thought we were partners
in this marriage.
(Bernadette:)We are. Stop it. And for the
last time, you're not fat.